Marcin Wojtczak

PROJECTS

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>Github</u> <u>Vercel</u>

Languages

• English - B2

In progress

Hobbies

NBA, II WW history, travel, cooking, sport.

CONTACT

531 787 144 marcinwojtczak.pure@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a former personal trainer, beginner developer. I have decided to change my career path and I have been committed to that idea totally since the last 3 years. Now, after finishing several courses and completing a few independent projects I am ready to undertake an entry-level job.

TRAININGS AND COURSES

06/2023 - freeCodeCamp - React Rauter 6 - Full Course

06/2023 - freeCodeCamp - Next.js Full Course For Beginners

01/2023 - freeCodeCamp - React Course

12/2022 - Brad Traversy - TypeScript Crash Course

08/2022 - Udemy - Modern JavaScript From The Beginning

07/2022 - Css/Html - Brad Traversy, Kevin Powell

01/2022 - freeCodeCamp - Python API Developer

12/2021 - freeCodeCamp - Learn PostgreSQL Tutorial

04/2021 - freeCodeCamp - Django for everybody

04/2021 - Corey Schafer - Python Django Tutorial

01/2021 - Udemy - Complete python developer: Zero to Mastery

11/2020 - Udemy - Data Science introduction in Python

05/2020 - Coursera - Python for everybody

EDUCATION

Uniwersytet Łódzki

Masters; Pedagogy of Physical and Health Culture 2006 - 2009

Wyższa Szkoła Humanistyczno - Ekonomiczna, Włocławek Bachelor; Pedagogy of Physical and Defense Education 2003 - 2006

CAREER SUMMARY

Co-founder GoFit, Personal Trainer

office-based trainings program

09/2018 - present

Personal Trainer

Pure Jatomi Polska

01/2013 - 01/2018

Bodybuilding Instructor, Personal Trainer

Various gyms and fitness clubs 12/2010 - 12/2012

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

I am ready to sign a loyalty agreement with my future employer.

I hereby give my consent for the processing of my personal data for the necessary purposes related to the recruitment process, in accordance with the Act of 10 May 2018 on the Protection of Personal Data (Journal of Laws of 2018, item 1000) and in line with the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (GDPR).